domainpromocodes.com 2017-06-06

# Domain Promo Codes - Privacy Policy

### If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us  at the contact page on our website which can be found here http://www.domainpromocodes.com/contact/

At http://www.domainpromocodes.com/, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by http://www.domainpromocodes.com/ and how it is used.

### **Personal İnformations**

### We dont collect any personal information such as your age , your name or gender . You are totally safe with us. 

### **Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, http://www.domainpromocodes.com/ makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons  **  
http://www.domainpromocodes.com/ does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie  **  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on http://www.domainpromocodes.com/.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to http://www.domainpromocodes.com/ and other sites on the Internet.   
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....  
Google Adsense  
Commission junction  
Private Affiliate Programs

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on http://www.domainpromocodes.com/ send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

http://www.domainpromocodes.com/ has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. Further, any deals on this site are provided as is. We have no responsibility on changes that are made to them from the providers of said offers. In that regard, no warranty is given or implied.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. http://www.domainpromocodes.com/'s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

### Safe Harbor

DomainPromoCodes.com complies with the US-EU Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. RetailMeNot has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, please visit [http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/)

DomainPromoCodes.com has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-EU Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR web site at [www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints](http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints) for more information and to file a complaint.

### **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

### **From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy to clarify our practices or to reflect new or different privacy practices, such as when we add new features to our Services.  Your continued access or use of the Services after any such changes become effective constitutes your acceptance of the Privacy Policy as revised. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information about our privacy practices.**
